Customize your Home screen by choosing
a background color or image.
In Settings,
go to Personalization > My color and background.
Choose My background.
To use a solid color, select it here.
Or use a picture by choosing one of these three options.
Select Achievement art to use the image from an achievement.
Choose a game, and then the achievement.
Select Set as background.
Custom image is any picture you have on a USB drive
plugged into your Xbox.
You’ll need the Media Player app to use this.
If you don’t have the app, you’ll be prompted to go to the store to install it.
In the Media Player app,
browse to the pictures on your USB drive.
Select the one you want,
then press the Menu button on your controller
and choose Set as background.
Choose Screenshot to get to the screenshots you’ve taken.
Highlight one, press the Menu button,
and then Set as background.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.